It smells good.
It's good.
No way!
Hello!
Today, we are going to make mixed
juice!
We are going to make mixed juice with 4
people.
We are going to make original mixed
juice.
We are going to make mixed juice
several times.
We are not going to tell others what we
are going to make.
So, we are going to make it in a way of
Yaminabe.
Oh!
Yaminabe!
She has been saying Yaminabe for a
year.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you feel like a teacher?
I do.
I know!
We are going to make it in a way of
Yaminabe.
So, please come in front of the camera
and show what you are going to put in.
We are going to mix it and pour it into
a cup.
So, you are going to guess what other 3
ingredients are in it.
I see.
Please prepare the ingredients.
Okay!
Let's get started!
Let's start with Ritsuki.
Okay!
My first guess is...
This one!
It's strawberry!
I'll go with...
Ta-da!
Chocolate mint ice cream!
I'll take a big one.
I'll take chocolate mint ice cream.
Wow!
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
I'll have milk.
I had this milk when I was in
elementary school.
I'm a teacher.
I chose this one.
It's crepe-full milk crepe.
I was going to put shortcake in it, but
I didn't have it.
So, I chose milk crepe.
I think it goes well with anything.
I'll have this one first.
I'll have milk crepe.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Oh!
It looks good!
It looks so good!
This is our first time,
but let's try it and tell them that we
put it in.
Let's do it!
Cheers!
Let's eat!
What is this?
It tastes good but it's a bit weird.
What is it?
It tastes good.
I think the one you put in is the
chocolate mint flavor.
Chocolate mint ice cream?
It's good.
I put milk in it.
It looks good.
I put milk crepe in it.
Cake?
It doesn't taste good.
It's strawberry.
You like it without milk crepe.
I like it because it has milk crepe.
I was eating the core of banana.
I was surprised that you were eating
the core of banana.
It's good.
It's like this.
I like it.
The second one is this.
It's a plumberry.
Please remove the seeds.
I'm going to put in...
Lemon!
But I think it will blend in well.
Hello!
Today I'm going to introduce...
Caesar dressing!
I'm a person who likes to do things on
the sly.
I thought Caesar dressing would make me
feel better.
So I chose it.
Please enjoy!
I chose...
Ohagi!
I love Ohagi!
Ohagi is my favorite food.
I think I can eat Ohagi with anything.
Please watch this video!
I will eat Ohagi with a special sauce.
Please subscribe!
This is the second time.
All mixed.
I'm nervous.
I'm sure it's a good idea.
I'm not sure.
It's smelly.
I don't want to drink it.
Cheers!
Ready?
Wow!
It's dressing.
I don't like aftertaste.
It's disgusting.
Please subscribe to this channel.
My guess is...
This one!
Caesar dressing, lemon, pickled plum,
and ohagi.
Pickled plum?
I got lemon, Caesar dressing, ohagi,
and sesame.
I got Caesar dressing, lemon, juice,
corn, and kimpira gobo.
These two are the same, right?
Caesar dressing, tartar sauce, lemon
juice, and ohagi.
Wait, I got lemon juice.
Lemon?
No, I noticed it.
Oh, my god.
I got it wrong.
No, no, no.
But, if Karen got ohagi, it means she
got it right.
I asked you to guess the answer.
One of you got all four right.
What?
Can you tell us what you put in the
salad?
I know what it is.
Ohagi.
I like it.
I'm sure.
Caesar dressing.
I got...
I don't know what it is, but I like the
flavor the most.
I'm so frustrated.
But, the flavor is dressing.
That's right.
It's not bad.
If I had put it on the salad without
prejudice, I would have been able to eat
it.
It's like this.
I should have drunk the dressing as it
is.
You should have developed a new
dressing recipe instead of mixing juice.
I see.
I'm so frustrated.
This is the product.
I love this.
Next, I'm going to make banana.
My ideal is chocolate banana.
Someone, please put chocolate in it.
Hello.
I'm back.
Ta-da.
This is a kiwi.
The reason why I chose kiwi is because
I like kiwi.
Kiwi is easy to cut.
I just cut it and scoop it with a
spoon.
Next, I'm going to make a persimmon.
This is my favorite.
I'm sure it will be delicious.
I'm going to make a persimmon.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Cheers!
It smells good.
What?
It's easy to get a cold.
I bought this perfume the other day.
It's not good.
No way.
Cheers!
I don't like it.
It smells like fireworks.
But one of them is really strong.
What is this?
I don't like it.
I don't know if I can drink such a bad
drink.
My guess is...
Banana, yuzu, pudding, kiwi.
I see.
Banana, kiwi, pudding, pumpkin.
It's easy to guess.
Custard, pumpkin salad, kiwi, sesame
dressing.
Kiwi, banana, wet persimmon,
strawberry.
It's a challenge.
No, no, no.
Please tell us what you put in your
drink.
I put pudding.
I put banana.
I put kiwi.
You are the worst.
If you put only these three, it would
be delicious.
I thought you would put salty drink
because it's the third drink.
I put banana because it's a smoothie.
I thought custard was not sold only in
the store.
You are amazing.
Rirei is amazing.
You didn't get the right answer this
time.
I'm frustrated.
Let's move on to the next question.
Please subscribe to this channel.
This is cream cheese.
Next, tofu.
I believe in the possibility of tofu
because there is tofu donut.
I chose strawberry syrup.
The reason is that I want to dye my
hair red.
I want to dye my hair red and make me
feel bad.
Next, Ani tofu.
This is the first time I ate this.
It's the first time I've eaten it all
in one sitting.
It's so cute!
It looks so good!
Cheers!
It's like a medicine.
It's like a cake.
I know what it is.
It's like condensed milk.
It's so sweet.
I can't eat sweet things.
Thank you for watching.
I got this one.
It's a cream cheese and carbonated
fruit jam.
It's tofu, red bean tofu, cream cheese
and fruit jam.
It's like fruit jam.
It's yogurt, grape, shaved ice,
strawberry, syrup and jam.
I'm so happy.
It's red bean tofu, strawberry powder,
condensed milk and water.
Powder?
I put some medicine in it.
I didn't know.
There is one person who got 3 out of 4
right.
Tachibana, you can start.
Thank you for watching.
Strawberry syrup.
Tofu.
Cream cheese.
Chitara, you got tofu.
Tofu?
I put tofu.
Rie is amazing.
She's been doing this from the
beginning.
She's a product development expert.
She's really amazing.
She's very precise.
She's amazing.
She's guessing who did it.
She's a professional.
Rie, you are amazing.
I got this!
Gummy!
Last one is...
It's edamame!
I thought it would be too plain,
so I made it into edamame.
I'm sure it'll be good.
I brought...
Aoi-jiru!
The reason is...
I brought this one-piece set of Tana
Toku's Manzuku-nabe.
I want you to put all of it in,
but I'll leave the rest to you.
Please.
I have something to apologize to you.
I've been thinking about making mixed
juice.
I thought it would be good if I brought
something salty.
So I bought crab miso.
I've been eating a lot of different
things.
I made a mistake in choosing this.
I'm sorry for the mistake.
I'm so sorry.
I have to tell you something.
I had to add water to the mixture.
So, only water is in the mixture.
I see.
Cheers!
I think I added milk to the mixture for
6 days.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What is this?
Wow, your mouth is green.
Maybe, but in some cases, chopsticks
may be necessary.
What is that?
What is this?
It's disgusting.
It's really muddy.
It's muddy.
It's a color tweet.
It's disgusting.
What is that?
Is it a bean? Black bean?
It's really disgusting.
What is this?
Only one person knows what it is.
It's scary.
It's green.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Oh, no!
I dropped it.
Are you OK?
If you put it around, it's OK.
I got it.
I don't know what it is.
Jitsuki chan?
Ok.
Mana friendly war with the members.
Tea
Foretaste
Green tea
I don't know the specific one.
Oats
Pumpkin salad, black beans, and green
juice.
Green juice, Koya tofu, crab miso, and
neri-keshi.
I'm sure it's wrong.
I didn't know.
I put neri-keshi in it, so I'm sure
it's wrong.
I'm sure it's wrong.
I didn't know.
There are two people who have three
answers.
Edamame.
I think there's a group.
I think it's either black beans or
green juice.
I didn't know it was wrong.
I didn't know.
Crab miso!
I thought crab miso was a mixture of
crab and miso.
But it was crab miso.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
So, we have 5 types of sweets.
If you have any questions, please try
them at home.
I don't recommend it.
I don't recommend it, either.
We will tell you which one is the best
among 5 types.
I see.
Rui and I liked the sweet one, but we
wanted to try the bitter one.
This one.
If you like super sweet one, you should
try it.
This is the one with wet.
I think it's the one with wet.
Oh, the one with wet.
I think it's not good.
So, the sweet one or the one with wet
is your choice.
We have a rich taste.
I've never had such a experience.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
U.S. Money Reserve